# Gustavo Adolfo Gonzalez Azuaje Illustrator//Graphic Designer//Web Developer

203 W 144 St, New York, NY
gustavogonz3393@gmail.com | 646 416 0199
gus-tavogonz.github.io | linkedin.com/in/gus-tavogonz | github.com/Gus-tavogonz

#### **Technical Skills**

- -Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, Adobe LightRoom, Cinema 4D
- -HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS, React, MySQL, MongoDB

#### **Professional Profile**

Graphic Artist with 5 years of experience in illustration, graphic design, animation, and web design. Experienced in all aspects of the design process, from conceptualization to final application. Offered support creating visual graphics for social media strategies, web design and presentations. Capable of working in a multitude of styles and media, maintening visual coherence for each project.

### **Work History**

# 2019 Freelance Graphic Designer at ETL Group - New York, NY

Digital Production Company offering services to Walter Baker, Sabe Masson and Arabian Oud Design emails, newsletters and digital assets for ecommerce clients.

Create templates for promotions and special offers, maintaining the visual style of each brand. Retouching photos and photo selections to be used on the clients website and social media.

## February 2017 to 2019 Office Manager at UNYPO LLC - New York, NY

# Property management company in the TriState area.

Create ads and copywriting to advertise rental units and attract potential clients renters and tenants. Keep bills, documents and vendors information on file.

#### July 2015 to August 2016 Graphic Designer at Ardyh Holdings C.A - Caracas, Venezuela

# Digital production company in charge of developing campaigns, marketing material and the realization of various events for a variety of clients

Conceptualize different aspects for the creation of new brands, from logo design and its applications, to catalogs that reflect the spirit and message of the brand.

Create social media graphics and marketing material to promote our clients brands and bolster a stronger digital presence in social media.

Work with a team of designers, assisting on all aspect for the production of graphics, from retouching and editing photographs to prepare illustrations and graphics to be animated.

# February 2015 May 2015 Graphic Designer at La Casa Productora - Caracas, Venezuela

# Full service digital agency in the area of web design, video production and marketing campaigns.

Assist in the design of web sites from a variety of clients, from online stores to make-up artists Create short animations and motion graphics for a variety of videos.

Create graphics, illustrations and 3d graphics for client presentations and licitations in order to secure new clients and bussinesses for our company

#### Education

2018 Columbia Engineering School certificate as Full Stack Developer - New York, NY

2011-2015 Illustration at Institute of Design of Caracas - Caracas, Venezuela

### Languages

English, Spanish